OLUWASEYI OSHINOWO

Norcross GA 30071 | 4045127734 | oshinowomodupe@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/oshinowo-oluwaseyi

Professional Summary

Successful professional with over 2-year experience in customer service environment, implementing measures to ensure that customers are well taken care off and their needs met by creating lots of empathy, communication skills which has given a 98% customer satisfaction approval, maximizing the call flow process to ensure that turnaround time is kept in check.

`_____

Skills

Excellent communication
 Process Improvement
 Customer relations
 Sales Management
 Data Analysis

.....

Experience

Insurance Customer Support specialist TTEC

11/2021 – present

- Communicating with clients to ensure that the needs are met
- Creating a friendly atmosphere of trust to ensure that the client's needs are met
- Actively listening to the client needs and quick response on the best approach
- Creating Empathy during the call duration
- Working as a team with others to ensure that organizational goal is achieved
- Ensures secrecy of cu personal and account information

Customer Support Agent

06/2021 - 11/2021

TTEC

- Maximized the call flow process to ensure 100% product delivery
- Created a friendly environment to build customers trust in company's products
- 100% engagement with team member that materialized to corporate objectives.

Warehouse Data Manager Nigerian Bottling Company (Coca Cola)

04/2009 - 02/2017

- Analyzed Product availability index (PAI) in all commercial territory, production location and selling location that led to 52% buffer stock
- Maintained effective functioning of Forklifts in relation to manpower that result in 15% decrease in idle manpower
- Analyzed One-way Pack product across all location which metamorphose into 3:5 plastic to bottle weekly increase
- Documented Sales loss analysis across all locations and compare with company baseline which induce 13% decrease in sale loss
- Stock Count Summary in all locations.
- Managed pallet Utilization and availability across all warehouses location that increase process chain flow and reduced annual cost by 36%

<u>Certification</u>	
 Licensed Agent in life Accident and Sickness 	08/2021
 Licensed Agent in Auto and Property causality 	11/2021
Education	
 Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp 	03/2022 - 09/2022
TY I ST SY SY	00/0011 10/0014
 University of Lagos, Nigeria 	03/2011 - 10/2014
Master's in Business Administration {MBA}	
Olabisi Onabanjo University, Nigeria	05/2002 - 08/2006
B.sc Physics with Electronics (Upper credit)	
2.50 Thysics was Electronics (Opper electro)	